[
    {
        "Question": "What can TACC users use MATLAB for?",
        "Answer Given": "\ncmd-line\nlogin1$",
        "Score": 0.001319351140409708,
        "Actual Answer": "only for non-commercial, academic purposes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I load MATLAB?",
        "Answer Given": "\n\n\n Viewing",
        "Score": 0.005332754459232092,
        "Actual Answer": "module load matlab"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Should I launch MATLAB jobs on login nodes?",
        "Answer Given": "\n\ncmd-line\nlogin1$",
        "Score": 0.008470006287097931,
        "Actual Answer": "Do NOT launch MATLAB on the login nodes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Where can I submit my MATLAB jobs?",
        "Answer Given": "\n\ncmd-line\nlogin1$",
        "Score": 0.005241368897259235,
        "Actual Answer": "on the TACC resources, e.g. Frontera, Stampede3, or Lonestar6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Why can I not use MATLAB on login nodes?",
        "Answer Given": "\n\ncmd-line\nlogin1$",
        "Score": 0.0043455432169139385,
        "Actual Answer": "This may fail and, more importantly, it will prevent other users from doing their work, as your execution will take up too many cycles on the shared login node"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I invoke MATLAB?",
        "Answer Given": "\n\n\n Viewing",
        "Score": 0.004180967342108488,
        "Actual Answer": "matlab"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the command to invoke MATLAB?",
        "Answer Given": "getfacl",
        "Score": 0.006721710320562124,
        "Actual Answer": "matlab"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the standard way to submit a Slurm job?",
        "Answer Given": "getfacl",
        "Score": 0.013982362113893032,
        "Actual Answer": "sbatch myjobscript"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I submit a Slurm job?",
        "Answer Given": "\ncmd-line\nlogin1$",
        "Score": 0.005389899015426636,
        "Actual Answer": "sbatch myjobscript"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How is using login nodes for MATLAB jobs system abuse?",
        "Answer Given": "\n\ncmd-line\nlogin1$",
        "Score": 0.001887749182060361,
        "Actual Answer": "it will prevent other users from doing their work, as your execution will take up too many cycles on the shared login node"
    }
]